Narrator: Do you speak English at work?
F: What do these people have in common: a banker in Mexico City,
a barman in a five-star hotel in Warsaw, and a worker in the Hitachi electronics factory in Tokyo.
They all speak English at work.
Do you speak English at work?
Write and tell us.
Narrator: Marcos
Marcos: I work in a restaurant in Madrid. I’m a waiter.
I speak English at work every day, because a lot of tourists come here.
I help customers with the menu and I say what the special dishes are.
They are very happy because they can talk to me in English.
A lot of tourists don’t speak Spanish, but they usually speak English.
Narrator: Charlotte
Charlotte: I’m a receptionist and I work in an office in Paris.
It’s a multinational company.
When people from other countries visit the company I need to welcome them in English.
I also need to answer the phone in English.
When we have meetings we all speak in English, because it’s the language of the company.